[
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What band released the Important record Punk is Ghetto in 1998?",
        "correct": "A//Political",
        "answerA": "A//Political",
        "answerB": "Algiers",
        "answerC": "The Saints",
        "answerD": "Anti- Flag"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Afrika Bambaataa teamed up with former Sex Pistols singer Johnny Lydon in 1984 to record the anti-fascist, anti-racist classic \"World Destruction.\" What was the name of their group?",
        "correct": "Time Zone",
        "answerA": "Time Zone",
        "answerB": "Death Zone",
        "answerC": "Fight Zone",
        "answerD": "War Zone"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This folk punk artist, and champion of feminist causes, began her music career by starting her own record label- Righteous Babe Records. Who is the Artist?",
        "correct": "Ani DiFranco",
        "answerA": "Ani DiFranco",
        "answerB": "Laura Jane Grace",
        "answerC": "Lucinda Williams",
        "answerD": "Tori Amos"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2004 U.S. Representative�Jim McDermott gave a speech on the�House Floor where he praised�this�radical leftist punk band for encouraging young people to vote.",
        "correct": "Anti-Flag",
        "answerA": "Anti-Flag",
        "answerB": "Rise Against",
        "answerC": "NOFX",
        "answerD": "Against All Authority"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The 1931 organized labor staple \"I Am a Union Women\" was written and sang by who?",
        "correct": "Aunt Molly Jackson",
        "answerA": "Aunt Molly Jackson",
        "answerB": "Sara Carter",
        "answerC": "Marion Harris",
        "answerD": "Bessie Smith"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The all female rock group Bad Larrys performed at this politician's New Hampshire rally for president in 2020.",
        "correct": "Bernie Sanders",
        "answerA": "Bernie Sanders",
        "answerB": "Kamala Harris",
        "answerC": "Joe Biden",
        "answerD": "Amy Klobuchar"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What year did the music effort \"Band Aid\" begin? 1984",
        "correct": "1984",
        "answerA": "1984",
        "answerB": "1980",
        "answerC": "1988",
        "answerD": "1986"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Ben Cohen and Jerry Greenfield's successful ice cream franchise rose to prominence through what music based subculture?",
        "correct": "The Deadheads",
        "answerA": "The Deadheads",
        "answerB": "The Juggalos",
        "answerC": "The Mods",
        "answerD": "Punks"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What label did the feminist punk band Bikini Kill release their 1996 record Reject All American?",
        "correct": "Kill Rock Stars",
        "answerA": "Kill Rock Stars",
        "answerB": "SST",
        "answerC": "Death Row Records",
        "answerD": "Lookout Records"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What's the name of radical folk singer Billy Bragg's first album?",
        "correct": "Life's Riot With Spy vs Spy",
        "answerA": "Life's Riot With Spy vs Spy",
        "answerB": "Worker's Playtime",
        "answerC": "England, Half English",
        "answerD": "Don't Try This at Home"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Where did the iconic rock magazine Rolling Stone get its name?",
        "correct": "All of the Above",
        "answerA": "The band of the same name",
        "answerB": "From the 1965 Bob Dylan song \"Like a Rolling Stone\"",
        "answerC": "All of the Above",
        "answerD": "From a Muddy Waters song released in 1950?"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-These two women, from the feminist punk band Bratmobile, are credited with coining the term \"Riot Grrrl.\"",
        "correct": "Allison Wolfe and Molly Neuman",
        "answerA": "Allison Wolfe and Molly Neuman",
        "answerB": "Kathleen Hanna and Tobi Vail",
        "answerC": "Kathi Wilcox and Molly Neuman",
        "answerD": "Sharon Cheslow and Courtney Love"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The song \"Why?\", a 1984 hit song by the group Bronski Beat about anti-gay prejudice and hate appeared on what important album?",
        "correct": "Age of Consent",
        "answerA": "Age of Consent",
        "answerB": "Truthdare Doubledare",
        "answerC": "Rainbow Nation",
        "answerD": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who did former Republican Governor of New Jersey Chris Christie say was his favorite artist?",
        "correct": "Bruce Springsteen",
        "answerA": "Bruce Springsteen",
        "answerB": "Toby Keith",
        "answerC": "Bon Jovi",
        "answerD": "Thin Lizzy"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Buffalo Springfield youth movement classic of the 1960's \"For What its Worth\" was remade by what hip-hop group in the late 1990's? ",
        "correct": "Public Enemy",
        "answerA": "Public Enemy",
        "answerB": "Dead Prez",
        "answerC": "Da Lynch Mob",
        "answerD": "X- Clan"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-During a 1977 episode of Sesame Street, who participated in the first representation of breastfeeding ever aired on television?",
        "correct": "Buffy Sainte- Marie",
        "answerA": "Buffy Sainte- Marie",
        "answerB": "Linda Ronstadt",
        "answerC": "Loretta Lynn",
        "answerD": "Olivia Newton-John"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The song \"Black Magic Women\" was originally written by Fleetwood Mac member Peter Green and was memorably sung by which member of Santana on their 1970 landmark album Abraxas? ",
        "correct": "Future Journey member, Greg Rolie",
        "answerA": "Carlos Santana",
        "answerB": "Guess singer Jimi Hendricks",
        "answerC": "Eric Burdon of the Animals",
        "answerD": "Future Journey member, Greg Rolie"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This UK based anarcho-punk band managed to reach mainstream success while staying true to their political convictions with popular songs like \"Tubthumping\" and \"Amnesia\" in the late 1990's. ",
        "correct": "Chumbawamba",
        "answerA": "Chumbawamba",
        "answerB": "Crass",
        "answerC": "Conflict",
        "answerD": "Sham 69"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The hip-Hop artist Common wrote \"A Song for Assata\" in 2000. Assata Shakur was a member of what black liberation organization of the 1970's and 80's?",
        "correct": "The Black Liberation Army",
        "answerA": "Blackstone Rangers",
        "answerB": "The Black Panther Party",
        "answerC": "The Black Liberation Army",
        "answerD": "Nation of Islam"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who was the lead singer for the UK based anarchist punk band Conflict?",
        "correct": "Colin Jerwood",
        "answerA": "Colin Jerwood",
        "answerB": "Steve Ignorant",
        "answerC": "Danny Lore",
        "answerD": "Stevie Ross"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What two groups named their records \"Steal This Album\" after the 1960's Yippie Abbie Hoffman's \"Steal this Book.\" ",
        "correct": "The hip-hop group the Coup and the alternative metal band System of a Down",
        "answerA": "The political hip-hop group the Coup and the alternative metal band System of a Down",
        "answerB": "The political hip- hop group Dead  Prez and the alternative metal band Rage Against the Machine",
        "answerC": "The hip-hop group The Roots and the alternative metal band Faith No More",
        "answerD": "The hip-hop group Gang Star and the alternative metal band Linkin Park"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This late seventies English punk band, which espoused anarchism and sung about the evils of war, patriarchy, consumer culture�and supported animal rights, started their own eponymously named record label.",
        "correct": "Crass",
        "answerA": "Crass",
        "answerB": "Black Flag",
        "answerC": "the Dead Milkmen",
        "answerD": "Agnostic Front"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who originally wrote and recorded the 1969 anti-war song \"Fortunate Son\"? ",
        "correct": "Credence Clearwater Revival",
        "answerA": "Credence Clearwater Revival",
        "answerB": "Foo Fighters",
        "answerC": "the Yardbirds",
        "answerD": "Cream"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Members of Public Enemy and Rage Against the Machine got together with this LA based hip-hop group in 2007 to create the group Prophets of Rage.",
        "correct": "Cypress Hill",
        "answerA": "Cypress Hill",
        "answerB": "Da Lynch Mob",
        "answerC": "Ozomatli",
        "answerD": "Dilated Peoples"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The political, independent, punk record label Alternative Tentacles was started by which band in San Francisco in 1978?",
        "correct": "Dead Kennedys",
        "answerA": "Dead Kennedys",
        "answerB": "The Avengers",
        "answerC": "Bomb",
        "answerD": "The Pansy Division"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The song Police State by the political hip-hop group Dead Prez appeared on what landmark 2000 album?",
        "correct": "Lets Get Free",
        "answerA": "Lets Get Free",
        "answerB": "Wake Up!",
        "answerC": "RBG: revolutionary but gangsta",
        "answerD": "Information Age"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Door's anti- Vietnam War song \"Unknown Soldier\" first appeared on which album in 1968? ",
        "correct": "Waiting for the Sun",
        "answerA": "Waiting for the Sun",
        "answerB": "Morrison Hotel",
        "answerC": "LA Women",
        "answerD": "Strange Days"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What US punk band from Rhode Island released the album Full Communism in 2015?",
        "correct": "Downtown Boys",
        "answerA": "Downtown Boys",
        "answerB": "The Island Boys",
        "answerC": "Black Dice",
        "answerD": "Arc Iris"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2019 the political folk-punk artist Even Greer released the song \"Ya Estamos\" a song about political resistance in the face of adversity, with which artist?",
        "correct": "Singer-songwriter and activist Taina Asili",
        "answerA": "Singer-songwriter and activist Taina Asili",
        "answerB": "Singer-songwriter and activist Ani DiFranco",
        "answerC": "Singer-songwriter and activist Kathleen Hanna",
        "answerD": "Singer-songwriter and activist Melissa Etheridge"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In what year did Frank Zappa & The Mothers of Invention's influential first album, Freak Out! come out?",
        "correct": "1966",
        "answerA": "1966",
        "answerB": "1969",
        "answerC": "1975",
        "answerD": "1978"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Fugazi, an early 1980's independent political punk band based in Washington DC, started which legendary record label?",
        "correct": "Discord",
        "answerA": "Discord",
        "answerB": "Touch and Go Records",
        "answerC": "Sub-Pop",
        "answerD": "Fat Wreck Records"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This member of the groundbreaking New York hip-hop group the Fugees decided to return to Haiti in 2010 where he was born and run for president. His canidancy was ultimately denied by the Provisional Electorial Council.",
        "correct": "Wyclef Jean",
        "answerA": "Wyclef Jean",
        "answerB": "Lauryn Hill",
        "answerC": "Pras Michel",
        "answerD": "\r\nChris Schwartz "
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What Gang of Four album was ranked the 5th greatest punk album of all time by Rolling Stone?",
        "correct": "Entertainment!",
        "answerA": "Entertainment!",
        "answerB": "Solid Gold",
        "answerC": "Songs of the Free",
        "answerD": "Mall"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What year was the classic reality rap song \"The Message\" by Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five released? ",
        "correct": "1981",
        "answerA": "1981",
        "answerB": "1974",
        "answerC": "1987",
        "answerD": "1984"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The hip hop artist Ice Cube pulled together and produced this LA�based black nationalist�rap group named after his record label.",
        "correct": "Da Lynch Mob",
        "answerA": "Da Lynch Mob",
        "answerB": "Westside Connection",
        "answerC": "EPMD",
        "answerD": "WC and the Maad Circle"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Peruvian American political hip-hop artist Immortal Technique appeared in this movie drama about the 2004 Republican National Convention in New York City.",
        "correct": "This Revolution",
        "answerA": "This Revolution",
        "answerB": "Our Revolution",
        "answerC": "My Revolution",
        "answerD": "Revolution Now"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This folk rock duo performed a concert in the Spring in 2016 to protest the United Methodist Church's ban on the ordination of practicing \"homosexuals\" and permitting same-sex couples to marry. ",
        "correct": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerA": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerB": "Wendy and Lisa",
        "answerC": "Ann and Nancy Wilson",
        "answerD": "Shakespear's Sister"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-On March 18 2016, 13 swat team members with the Fayetteville police department raided this rappers recording studio in North Carolina. Who was it?",
        "correct": "J.Cole",
        "answerA": "J.Cole",
        "answerB": "Kendrick Lamar",
        "answerC": "21 Savage",
        "answerD": "Drake"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The 1986 album Lives in the Balance, a record full of songs critical of U.S. imperialism and militarism, is perhaps the most political album by this U.S. rock musician and singer.",
        "correct": "Jackson Brown",
        "answerA": "Jackson Brown",
        "answerB": "Don Henley",
        "answerC": "Tom Petty",
        "answerD": "James Taylor"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Radical folk singer Joan Baez founded this anti- war non-profit in 1964?",
        "correct": "Institute for the Study of Nonviolence",
        "answerA": "Institute for the Study of Nonviolence",
        "answerB": "Institue for World Peace",
        "answerC": "Coalition to End Violence",
        "answerD": "School for Peace and Reconcilation"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2018 pop singer John Legend came out in support of what Florida state ballot measure?",
        "correct": "Amendment 4 to restore voting rights to ex-prisoners.",
        "answerA": "Amendment 4 to restore voting rights to ex-prisoners.",
        "answerB": "Measure 13 to ban undocumented immigrants from voting.",
        "answerC": "Inititative 204 to ban discrimination against LGBTQI in state employment",
        "answerD": "ACT 12 to reinstate affirmative action in university admissions"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What was the name of the t-shirt line Kathleen Hanna launched in 2018 which aims to provide funding for the school tuition of girls in West Africa? a) Shirts for Sierra Leone; b) Tees 4 Togo; c) T-shirts for Niger; d) MaliTees?  b) Tees 4 Togo",
        "correct": "Tees 4 Togo",
        "answerA": "Tees 4 Togo",
        "answerB": "Shirts for Sierra Leone",
        "answerC": "T-shirts for Niger",
        "answerD": "MaliTees"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Compton, California native Kendrick Lamar won a Grammy Award in 2015 for what?",
        "correct": "Best Rap Album (To Pimp a Butterfly)",
        "answerA": "Best Rap Album (To Pimp a Butterfly)",
        "answerB": "2015 Best New Artist",
        "answerC": "Best Pop Album (Section.80)",
        "answerD": "Lifetime Achievement Award"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Killer Mike, political rapper and hip-hop activist based in Atlanta, Georgia endorsed which presidential candidate in 2016?",
        "correct": "Bernie Sanders",
        "answerA": "Bernie Sanders",
        "answerB": "Jill Stein",
        "answerC": "Joe Biden",
        "answerD": "Michelle Obama"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2019 the record Omoiyari, a concept album about the internment of Japanese Americans during World War II was released by which Seattle based violinist?",
        "correct": "Kishi Bashi",
        "answerA": "Kishi Bashi",
        "answerB": "Ami Nakashima",
        "answerC": "Haruomi Hosono",
        "answerD": "Keiji Haino"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The classic anti-policing song \"Sound of da Police\" came out in 1990. Which legendary patriarch of political rap wrote and recorded the song? ",
        "correct": "KRS-One",
        "answerA": "KRS-One",
        "answerB": "Kool G Rap",
        "answerC": "Big Daddy Kane",
        "answerD": "Nas"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-According to Leonard Cohen in this 1992 song off his album The Future what is coming to USA?",
        "correct": "Democracy",
        "answerA": "Democracy",
        "answerB": "Fascism",
        "answerC": "a race war",
        "answerD": "Socialism"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who's was lead singer for the electro-punk band LeTigre?",
        "correct": "Kathleen Hanna",
        "answerA": "Kathleen Hanna",
        "answerB": "Molly Neuman",
        "answerC": "Kathi Wilcox",
        "answerD": "Tobi Vail"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Artists United Against Apartheid created a benefit album dedicated to funding groups working to end apartheid in South Africa in 1985. What was the name of the record?",
        "correct": "Sun City",
        "answerA": "Sun City",
        "answerB": "Holiday City",
        "answerC": "Sun Town",
        "answerD": "Sunny Inn City"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In the Fugees song \"The Beast\" off their amazing 1996 hip-hop album The Score, which Republican politician \"Sucks Dick?\"",
        "correct": "Newt Gingrich",
        "answerA": "Newt Gingrich",
        "answerB": "John Kasich",
        "answerC": "Joe Scarborough",
        "answerD": "Henry Hyde"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What song did these lyrics come from? \"I really think the war on terror is a bunch of bullshit, Just a poor excuse for you to use up all your bullets, Limbaugh is a racist. Glenn Beck is a racist, Gaza Strip was getting bombed and Obama didn't say shit.\"",
        "correct": "\"Words I never Said\"-Lupe Fiasco",
        "answerA": "\"Words I never Said\"-Lupe Fiasco",
        "answerB": "\"Lies, Lies and More Lies\"- Common",
        "answerC": "\"Talk Show Hypocrites\"- Kendrick Lamar",
        "answerD": "\"Singin' Truth to Power\"- Drake"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In the 1971 classic album \"What's Going On\" this soul artist tackles everything from racism to the Vietnam War to environmental degradation. Who was the artist? ",
        "correct": "Marvin Gaye",
        "answerA": "Marvin Gaye",
        "answerB": "Curtis Mayfield",
        "answerC": "Stevie Wonder",
        "answerD": "Smoky Robinson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who was the manager of the proto- punk political rock band MC5 in the late 1960's?",
        "correct": "John Sinclair",
        "answerA": "John Sinclair",
        "answerB": "Jack Casady",
        "answerC": "Allen Ginsburg",
        "answerD": "Jerry Rubin"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which record label first distributed the conscious hip-hop and world music artist Michael Franti?",
        "correct": "Alternative Tentacles",
        "answerA": "Alternative Tentacles",
        "answerB": "Anti-",
        "answerC": "Six Degrees Records",
        "answerD": "Capitol"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Michelle Shocked's second album, released in 1988, takes its name from a speaking part in the Pink Floyd song \"Us and Them.\" What the name of the album?",
        "correct": "Short, Sharp, Shocked",
        "answerA": "Short, Sharp, Shocked",
        "answerB": "I was really drunk at the time",
        "answerC": "Matter of fact it's all dark",
        "answerD": "I Can't Recall"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This lead singer of the left-wing Australian alternative rock group Midnight Oil was a Representative for Kingsford Smith, New South Wales in Australia's national parliament.",
        "correct": "Peter Garrett",
        "answerA": "Peter Garrett",
        "answerB": "Bon Scott",
        "answerC": "Jim Kerr",
        "answerD": "Matt Johnson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This Austin, Texas punk band that goes by the acronym MDC was a force in the U.S. hardcore scene in the early 1980's. What does MDC stand for?",
        "correct": "Millions of Dead Cops",
        "answerA": "Millions of Dead Cops",
        "answerB": "Millions of Dead Corpses",
        "answerC": "More Dot-Coms",
        "answerD": "Many Dead Corporate CEO's"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Jello Biafra, former lead singer for the Dead Kennedys, and Al Jourgensen of the Chicago based industrial band Ministry teamed up to create this political band.",
        "correct": "Lard",
        "answerA": "Lard",
        "answerB": "Scarred",
        "answerC": "Mole",
        "answerD": "Yeast"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-MMG was a Revolutionary Communist Party affiliated hip-hop collective from New York that recorded a pro-U.S. flag burning song back in 1990. What's the name of the song?",
        "correct": "\"Burn Baby Burn\"",
        "answerA": "\"Burn Baby Burn\"",
        "answerB": "\"50 State Fire\"",
        "answerC": "\"Old Glory in Flames\"",
        "answerD": "\"Burn the Flag\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2017 this Muslim rapper from Flint, Michigan released a song defending women who choose to wear Hijabs called \"Hijabi (Wrap my Hijab).\" What's her name?",
        "correct": "Mona Hayder",
        "answerA": "Mona Hayder",
        "answerB": "Shadia Mansour",
        "answerC": "Mayam Mahmoud",
        "answerD": "Felukah"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Fat Mike, is the politically active lead singer of this US punk band popular in the 1990s.",
        "correct": "NOFX",
        "answerA": "NOFX",
        "answerB": "Pennywise",
        "answerC": "The Offspring",
        "answerD": "Papa Roach"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This influential, political blues, folk singer and guitarist from Birmingham, Alabama sang \"O'freedom\" at the historic March on Washington for civil rights and jobs.",
        "correct": "Odetta",
        "answerA": "Odetta",
        "answerB": "Etta James",
        "answerC": "Eartha Kitt",
        "answerD": "Lena Horne"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In September 2018 Patti Smith performed an LA benefit show for this nonprofit organization who help musicians, artists and activists to highlight solutions to climate change.",
        "correct": "Pathways to Paris",
        "answerA": "Pathways to Paris",
        "answerB": "The Carbon Zero Committee",
        "answerC": "Coalition to Save the Planet",
        "answerD": "The Green Project"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Seattle based grunge rock band Pearl Jam endorse which progressive consumer advocate and Green Party nominee for president in 2000?",
        "correct": "Ralph Nader",
        "answerA": "Ralph Nader",
        "answerB": "Ross Perot",
        "answerC": "Jill Stein",
        "answerD": "John Anderson"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 1940 this political folk \"super group\" which included Pete Seeger, Lee Hays, Woody Guthrie, and Millard Lampell started singing and appearing together under what name?",
        "correct": "The  Almanac Singers",
        "answerA": "The  Almanac Singers",
        "answerB": "The Popular Front",
        "answerC": "The Unamericans",
        "answerD": "Global Voices"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who were the two female members of the folk protest group the Almanac Singers in the 1940's",
        "correct": "Agnes \"Sis\" Cunningham�and Bess Lomax Hawes",
        "answerA": "Agnes \"Sis\" Cunningham�and Bess Lomax Hawes",
        "answerB": "Aunt Molly Jackson and Sara Carter",
        "answerC": "Marion Harris and Bessie Smith",
        "answerD": "Mary Johnston and Gina Jones"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The folk trio Peter, Paul and Mary recorded the top ten hit? \"If I Had a Hammer\" in 1962. Who originally wrote the song?",
        "correct": "Pete Seeger and Lee Hayes",
        "answerA": "Pete Seeger and Lee Hayes",
        "answerB": "Woody Guthrie",
        "answerC": "Millard Lampell and Bob Dylan",
        "answerD": "Phil Ochs"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This third wave feminist, alternative rocker from the UK released the album Dry in 1992 to critical and popular acclaim. Who is she?",
        "correct": "PJ Harvey",
        "answerA": "PJ Harvey",
        "answerB": "Tori Amos",
        "answerC": "Bjork",
        "answerD": "Fiona Apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-How did the radical, folk musician Phil Ochs die?",
        "correct": "Suicide",
        "answerA": "Suicide",
        "answerB": "Murder",
        "answerC": "Cancer",
        "answerD": "AIDS"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Poor Righteous Teachers, a socially conscious hip-hop group big in the late eighties and early nineties, were a part of what New York based soci-spiritual movement?",
        "correct": "The Five Percent Nation",
        "answerA": "The Five Percent Nation",
        "answerB": "The Three Percent Nation",
        "answerC": "The One Percent Nation",
        "answerD": "The 10 Percent Nation"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This long running independent anarchist punk collective based in Minneapolis, Minnesota has published a zine and has ran a record label since 1989. What's its name?",
        "correct": "Profane Existence",
        "answerA": "Profane Existence",
        "answerB": "Positive Force",
        "answerC": "Maximum Rock-n-Roll",
        "answerD": "On Our Backs"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which list of artists were all part of the political rap-rock \"super group\" Prophets of Rage? ",
        "correct": "Tim Commerford, Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, and B-Real",
        "answerA": "Tim Commerford, Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, and B-Real",
        "answerB": "Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, B-Real and Ice Cube",
        "answerC": "Tim Commerford, Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, and Flea",
        "answerD": "Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, B-Real and Snoop Dogg"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This progressive rock band from the UK released the 1977 record \"Animals,\" an angry concept album loosely based on George Orwell's allegorical novel about class society of the same name.",
        "correct": "Pink Floyd",
        "answerA": "Pink Floyd",
        "answerB": "Led Zeppelin",
        "answerC": "Genesis",
        "answerD": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The famous film maker Spike Lee partnered with this political hip-hip group in the late 1980's to produce the main song- \"Fight the Power\"- in the sound track to his movie Do the Right Thing. ",
        "correct": "Public Enemy",
        "answerA": "Public Enemy",
        "answerB": "X-Clan",
        "answerC": "Paris",
        "answerD": "Run-DMC"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Swedish anti-authoritarian, punk band Refused released this highly acclaimed album on October 27, 1998 shortly before they broke up.",
        "correct": "The Shape of Punk to Come",
        "answerA": "The Shape of Punk to Come",
        "answerB": "War Music",
        "answerC": "Freedom",
        "answerD": "Operation Headfirst"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What 1989 album by REM is still considered their most openly political by many fans?",
        "correct": "Green",
        "answerA": "Green",
        "answerB": "Automatic for the People",
        "answerC": "Document",
        "answerD": "Fables of the Reconstruction"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which one of these bands never released a song about a \"racist friend?\" ",
        "correct": "Rise Against",
        "answerA": "Rise Against",
        "answerB": "Special AKA",
        "answerC": "They Might Be Giants",
        "answerD": "Naomi Pilgrim"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What religion did singer/ song writer Sinead O'Conner convert to in 2018?",
        "correct": "Islam",
        "answerA": "Islam",
        "answerB": "Southern Baptist",
        "answerC": "Buddhism",
        "answerD": "Confucianism"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 1979 this feminist punk band released the song \"Typical Girl\" which challenged traditional gender roles in society. ",
        "correct": "The Slits",
        "answerA": "The Slits",
        "answerB": "The Bags",
        "answerC": "X-Ray Specs",
        "answerD": "The Runaways"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The UK rapper Slowthai released this album in 2019 with songs critical of Brexit and Theresa May.",
        "correct": "Nothing Great About Britain",
        "answerA": "Nothing Great About Britain",
        "answerB": "I Wish I Knew",
        "answerC": "God Made the Queen",
        "answerD": "This Ain't England"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What year did the classic Sly and the Family Stone album There's a Riot Goin On get released?",
        "correct": "1971",
        "answerA": "1971",
        "answerB": "1975",
        "answerC": "1966",
        "answerD": "1979"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who did Snoop Dogg endorse for president in 2016?",
        "correct": "Hillary Clinton",
        "answerA": "Hillary Clinton",
        "answerB": "Bernie Sanders",
        "answerC": "Donald Trump",
        "answerD": "Kamala Harris"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This Denver based indy hip- hop anarchist released the 2013 album No Wising Up, No Settling Down in which he declared \"I Think I'm Emma Goldman.\"",
        "correct": "Sole",
        "answerA": "Sole",
        "answerB": "J. Cole",
        "answerC": "Macklemore",
        "answerD": "emcee lynx"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2001 this norte�o band from San Jos�, California sang \"Let me remind the gringo, that I didn't cross the border, the border crossed me\" in \"Somos M�s Americanos\" (\"We Are More American\") What's the name of the group?",
        "correct": "Los Tigres del Norte",
        "answerA": "Los Tigres del Norte",
        "answerB": "Los Tucanes de Tijuana",
        "answerC": "Vicente \"Chente\" Fern�ndez G�mez",
        "answerD": "Intocable"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The New York based no wave band Sonic Youth teamed up with Ian MaKay of Fugazi in 1992 to record this anti- fascist song.",
        "correct": "\"Youth Against Fascism\"",
        "answerA": "\"Youth Against Fascism\"",
        "answerB": "\"We Will Not Be Silent\"",
        "answerC": "\"The Anti-Nazi Salute\" ",
        "answerD": "\"Fuck Fascism\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The 1991 rap hit \"Free South Africa\" appeared on which Stetsasonic album? ",
        "correct": "Blood, Sweat and no Tears",
        "answerA": "Blood, Sweat and no Tears",
        "answerB": "In Full Gear",
        "answerC": "On Fire",
        "answerD": "Just Say Stet"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-On what 1976 did album Steve Miller's anti-poverty song \"Fly Like an Eagle\" appear? ",
        "correct": "Fly Like an Eagle",
        "answerA": "Fly Like an Eagle",
        "answerB": "Sailor",
        "answerC": "Book of Dreams",
        "answerD": "The Joker"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Stiff Little Fingers song \"Alternative Ulster\" was about what?",
        "correct": "The oppression of Northern Ireland youth by the Royal Ulster Constabulary",
        "answerA": "The oppression of Northern Ireland youth by the Royal Ulster Constabulary",
        "answerB": "The oppression of Northern Ireland Catholics by the Orange Order",
        "answerC": "The oppression of Women in Northern Ireland by Men",
        "answerD": "The oppression of Irish Protestants by the Vatican"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What year did the UK anarchist punk band the Subhumans start?",
        "correct": "1980",
        "answerA": "1980",
        "answerB": "1988",
        "answerC": "1977",
        "answerD": "1983"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which political Southern California hardcord punk band released the album Lights, Camera, Revolution in 1990?",
        "correct": "Suicidal Tendencies",
        "answerA": "Suicidal Tendencies",
        "answerB": "Agent Orange",
        "answerC": "Black Flag",
        "answerD": "Social Distortion"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Canadian based punk band Sum 41 released the political album Order in Decline in what year?",
        "correct": "2019",
        "answerA": "2019",
        "answerB": "1980",
        "answerC": "1992",
        "answerD": "2011"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In what year did Sweet Honey in the Rock perform at the Obama White House?",
        "correct": "2008",
        "answerA": "2008",
        "answerB": "2018",
        "answerC": "2002",
        "answerD": "2012"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The 2005 anti-war song B.Y.O.B. off the System of a Down album Mezmerize starts off with what question?",
        "correct": " \"Why do they always send the poor?\"",
        "answerA": " \"Why do they always send the poor?\"",
        "answerB": "\"Why do they treat us like whores?\"",
        "answerC": "\"Why do they always kill the poor\"",
        "answerD": "\"Time has come to settle the score\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The American rapper and political activist Talib Kweli teamed up with Mos Def in 1997 to form this influential hip-hop group.",
        "correct": "Black Star",
        "answerA": "Black Star",
        "answerB": "Wu-Tang Clan",
        "answerC": "Onyx",
        "answerD": "Black Sheep"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Tupac Shakar's mother, Afeni Shakur, was part of what black liberation organization in the 1970's?",
        "correct": "The Black Panther Party",
        "answerA": "The Black Panther Party",
        "answerB": "Black Liberation Army",
        "answerC": "NAACP",
        "answerD": "The Urban League"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This politically engaged artist from the UK, which released popular alternative albums in the 1980's and early 90's, recorded a song called \"The Beaten Generation\" lamenting Generation X political apathy.",
        "correct": "The The",
        "answerA": "The The",
        "answerB": "Midnight Oil",
        "answerC": "Simple Minds",
        "answerD": "U2"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-ONE is an international foundation created to end extreme poverty and preventable disease in Africa. Who started it?",
        "correct": "Bono of U2",
        "answerA": "Bono of U2",
        "answerB": "Peter Gabriel",
        "answerC": "Peter Garrett of Midnight Oil",
        "answerD": "Bob Geldof of the Boomtwon Rats"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which country singer said in 2015 \"I'm a great Bernie and Hillary fan, you know?\"",
        "correct": "Willie Nelson",
        "answerA": "Willie Nelson",
        "answerB": "Toby Keith",
        "answerC": "Keith Urban",
        "answerD": "Tim McGraw"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The late Lumumba Carson, better known as Professor X the Overseer, was a black nationalist, Brooklyn based, rapper with what politically oriented hip-hop group in the late 1980's and early 90's?",
        "correct": "X-Clan",
        "answerA": "X-Clan",
        "answerB": "the Last Poets",
        "answerC": "Brand Nubian",
        "answerD": "Poor Righteous Teachers"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The 1977 feminist, punk rock classic \"Oh Bondage Up Yours\" was written and performed by what English punk band?",
        "correct": "X- Ray Specs",
        "answerA": "X- Ray Specs",
        "answerB": "Hole",
        "answerC": "The Bags",
        "answerD": "The Slits"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Afrika Bambaataa, widely considered the�creator of electro- funk and an influential hip- hop innovator, founded what South Bronx based hip- hop organization in 1973?",
        "correct": "the Universal Zulu Nation",
        "answerA": "the Universal Zulu Nation",
        "answerB": "Boogie Down Productions",
        "answerC": "Hip Hop Congress",
        "answerD": "Hip hop for Change"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The song \"Hello Birmingham\" by Ani DiFranco is about what?",
        "correct": " The 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama",
        "answerA": " The 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama",
        "answerB": "The murder of Kansas abortion provider George Tiller in 2009",
        "answerC": "The murder of Florida abortion provider Dr. David Gunn in 1993",
        "answerD": "The bombing of the 16th Street Church in Birmingham, Alabama that killed four black girls in 1963"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Why was \"Band Aid\" created? ",
        "correct": "To help end a famine in Ethiopia",
        "answerA": "To help end a famine in Ethiopia",
        "answerB": "To help war refugees in Ethiopia",
        "answerC": "To help victims of a deadly typhoon in Ethiopia",
        "answerD": "To help victims of the Ebola Virus in Ethiopia"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Finish the title of this Joe Hill song written in 1913 and cover in 1984 by Billy Bragg. \"There is power in a _______\"? ",
        "correct": "Union",
        "answerA": "union",
        "answerB": "family",
        "answerC": "friendship",
        "answerD": "nation"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The youth movement anthem \"The Times They Are a-Changin\" by Bob Dylan first appeared on what 1964 album? ",
        "correct": "The Times They Are a-Changin",
        "answerA": "The Times They Are a-Changin",
        "answerB": "\r\nHighway 61 Revisited",
        "answerC": "Bringing It All Back Home",
        "answerD": "Another Side of Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What year did the all gay, synth rock trio Bronski Beat form in England?",
        "correct": "1983",
        "answerA": "1983",
        "answerB": "1988",
        "answerC": "1990",
        "answerD": "1978"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 1996, she started a philanthropic non-profit fund Nihewan Foundation for American Indian Education devoted to improving Native American students participation in learning.",
        "correct": "Buffy Sainte-Marie",
        "answerA": "Buffy Sainte-Marie",
        "answerB": "Tanya Tagaq",
        "answerC": "Joni Michell",
        "answerD": "Joan Baez"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What Latin rock legend founded the Milagro Foundation, which helps disadvantaged youth through grants and donations.",
        "correct": "Carlos Santana",
        "answerA": "Carlos Santana",
        "answerB": "Michael Carabello",
        "answerC": "Jose Chepito Areas",
        "answerD": "Ritchie Valens"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Black America Again, released in 2016, was the 11th studio album by which political hip-hop artist?",
        "correct": "Common",
        "answerA": "Common",
        "answerB": "Drake",
        "answerC": "Lil Wayne",
        "answerD": "Travis Scott"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In what year did the folk rock band Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young receive a Grammy for Best New Artist of the Year?",
        "correct": "1970",
        "answerA": "1970",
        "answerB": "1965",
        "answerC": "1974",
        "answerD": "1978"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In the 1993 Cypress Hill song \"I Want to Get High\" which politician did the group encourage to \"go and inhale?\" ",
        "correct": "Bill Clinton",
        "answerA": "Bill Clinton",
        "answerB": "Al Gore",
        "answerC": "Gary Hart",
        "answerD": "John Edwards"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Dead Kennedys lead singer Jello Biafra ran for this seat in San Francisco in the 1980's.",
        "correct": "Mayor",
        "answerA": "Mayor",
        "answerB": "City Council",
        "answerC": "Board of Supervisors",
        "answerD": "Attorney General"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What song did these lyrics come from? \"These record labels slang our tapes like dope, You could be next in line to sign and still be rhymes and broke, You'd rather have a Lexus or justice? A dream or some substance?\"�",
        "correct": "�\"Hip Hop\" by Dead Prez",
        "answerA": "�\"Hip Hop\" by Dead Prez",
        "answerB": "\"Hip Pop\" by Michael Franti & Spearhead ",
        "answerC": "\"Hip Rock\" by the Coup",
        "answerD": "\"Sheep to Slaughter\" by Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Why was Jim Morrison, lead singer of the Doors, arrested in New Haven, Connecticut in 1967?",
        "correct": "Disturbing the peace after being maced backstage and disparaging the police officer who did it after the incident while on stage.",
        "answerA": "Disturbing the Peace and Resisting Arrest after being maced backstage and disparaging the police officer who did it after the incident while on stage.",
        "answerB": "Lewd and Lasivious Behavior after getting caught having sex with a women backstage",
        "answerC": "Assault on a Peace Officer after  pushing and shoving a cop who broke up a make out session between Morrison and a fan",
        "answerD": "He wasn't arrested in New Haven in 1987"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This seminal hip- hop group�was responsible for popularizing socially conscious hip-hop in the early 1980's with classics like \"the Message\" and \"New York, New York.\"",
        "correct": "Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five",
        "answerA": "Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five",
        "answerB": "Run DMC",
        "answerC": "The Sugar Hill Gang",
        "answerD": "The treacherous three"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The East Bay radical political hip- hop artist Paris invited this New York based rapper on an extended mix track of the song \"Field Nigga Boogie\" off his 2003 album Sonic Jihad. ",
        "correct": "Immortal Technique",
        "answerA": "Immortal Technique",
        "answerB": "Slick Rick",
        "answerC": "LL Cool J",
        "answerD": "Master P"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Winona LaDuke, a Native American activist and former Green Party candidate for office, teamed up with this folk rock duo to start the grassroots environmental group Honor the Earth.",
        "correct": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerA": "Indigo Girls",
        "answerB": "Simon and  Garfunkel",
        "answerC": "Captain and Tennille",
        "answerD": "Hall and Oats"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-J. Cole's \"High for Hours,\" released in early 2017, mentioned a meeting with which president?",
        "correct": "Barack Obama",
        "answerA": "Barack Obama",
        "answerB": "Bill Clinton",
        "answerC": "George W Bush",
        "answerD": "Donald Trump"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-KRS-1, considered by many the father of the \"Golden Age\" of Hip-hip, kick off that era with what politically conscious hit in 1988?",
        "correct": "\"My Philosophy\" ",
        "answerA": "\"My Philosophy\" ",
        "answerB": "\"My Theory\"",
        "answerC": "\"My Thesis\"",
        "answerD": "\"My Beliefs\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Steven Van Zant, guitarist and longtime member of Bruce Springsteen's E Street Band, was the founder of what anti racist organization in the mid 1980's?",
        "correct": "Artist United Against Apartheid",
        "answerA": "Artist United Against Apartheid",
        "answerB": "Artist United Against Racism",
        "answerC": "Artist United Against White Supremacy",
        "answerD": "Artist United Against Bigotry"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 1985 what British weekly music magazine voted the landmark political album \"What's Going On\" by Marvin Gaye the best album of all time? ",
        "correct": "NME",
        "answerA": "NME",
        "answerB": "Melody Maker",
        "answerC": "Spin",
        "answerD": "The Globe"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-John Sinclair, manager for the MC5, founded what counter culture radical organization in Detroit back in late 1960's?",
        "correct": "the White Panther Party",
        "answerA": "the White Panther Party",
        "answerB": "Students for a Democratic Society",
        "answerC": "Youth International Party",
        "answerD": "the Weather Underground"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2007 Peter Garrett, writer of the anti-colonialism song Beds are Burning was named minister to this post in the  Australian government.",
        "correct": "Environmental",
        "answerA": "Environmental",
        "answerB": "Culture",
        "answerC": "Defense",
        "answerD": "Treasury"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In June 1988, this female, punk artist released the album Dream of Life, which included the politically charged song \"People Have the Power.\"",
        "correct": "Patti Smith",
        "answerA": "Patti Smith",
        "answerB": "Joan Jett",
        "answerC": "Debbie Harry",
        "answerD": "Siouxsie and the Banshees"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Eddie Vedder recorded  \"Against the 70's\" a song about how the baby boomer generation markets its own nostalgia to the youth about the politically vapid \"me decade.\" Who did he sing this duet with?",
        "correct": "Carla Bozulich",
        "answerA": "Carla Bozulich",
        "answerB": "Molly Neuman",
        "answerC": "Laura Macfarlane",
        "answerD": "Meg White"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who wrote and sang the 1961 anti- war folk song \"Where have All the Flowers Gone?",
        "correct": "Pete Seeger",
        "answerA": "Pete Seeger",
        "answerB": "Utah Phillips",
        "answerC": "Woody Guthrie",
        "answerD": "Phil Ochs"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Widely considered the most significant classic rock band reunion in decades, Pink Floyd played their last show together in 2005 at this benefit to end poverty in Africa.",
        "correct": "Live 8",
        "answerA": "Live 8",
        "answerB": "Cancel the Debt",
        "answerC": "Love 8",
        "answerD": "Campaign for global reparations"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What was the name of this anti-war hit song REM recorded on their 1989 album Green?",
        "correct": " \"Orange Crush\"",
        "answerA": " \"Orange Crush\"",
        "answerB": "\"Ignoreland\"",
        "answerC": "\"Begin The Begin\"",
        "answerD": "\"Turn You Inside-Out\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What's the name of Sinead O'Conner's first album?",
        "correct": "The Lion and the Cobra",
        "answerA": "The Lion and the Cobra",
        "answerB": "I Do Not Want What I Haven't Got\"",
        "answerC": "Universal Mother",
        "answerD": "Faith and Courage"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-South Youth recorded the punk single \"Kool Thing\"- a song about how some white women fetishize black male sexuality- with a cameo from this radical hip-hop artist in 1990. ",
        "correct": "Chuck D",
        "answerA": "Chuck D",
        "answerB": "LL Cool J",
        "answerC": "Cool Moe Dee",
        "answerD": "Ice Cube"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Dr. Bernice Johnson Reagon founded this  all-female, African-American cappella ensemble.",
        "correct": "Sweet Honey in the Rock",
        "answerA": "Sweet Honey in the Rock",
        "answerB": "the Chiffons",
        "answerC": "the Supremes",
        "answerD": "the Shirelles"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What year did the LA based, political metal band System of a Down release their album Toxicity?",
        "correct": "2001",
        "answerA": "2001",
        "answerB": "1997",
        "answerC": "2010",
        "answerD": "2017"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which Vice President went on TV to attack Tupac Shakar's first album 2pacalypse Now in 1991 blaming it for a police officer?s death in Texas.",
        "correct": "Dan Quayle",
        "answerA": "Dan Quayle",
        "answerB": "Al Gore",
        "answerC": "Dick Cheney",
        "answerD": "Nelson Rockefeller"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What was the U2 song \"Bullet the Blue Sky\" off the 1986 album Joshua Tree about? ",
        "correct": "US military intervention in El Salvador",
        "answerA": "US military intervention in El Salvador",
        "answerB": "US military intervention in the Middle East",
        "answerC": "US military intervention in the Balkans",
        "answerD": "US military intervention in Northern Ireland"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who was the lead singer of X-Ray Specs?",
        "correct": "Poly Styrene",
        "answerA": "Poly Styrene",
        "answerB": "Viv Albertine",
        "answerC": "Pauline Black",
        "answerD": "Eve Libertine"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Who started Band Aid?",
        "correct": "Bob Geldof and Midge Ure",
        "answerA": "Bob Geldof and Midge Ure",
        "answerB": "Boy George and Midge Ure",
        "answerC": "Bob Geldof and Bono",
        "answerD": "Bono and Jim Kerr"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In August of 1991 the Latino hip-hop group Cypress Hill did what?",
        "correct": "Released their first album",
        "answerA": "Released their first album",
        "answerB": "Played their first show",
        "answerC": "Opened the Lollapalooza festival",
        "answerD": "Break up for the first time"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The 1979 Vietnam War film \"Apocalypse Now\" featured what Doors Classic? ",
        "correct": "\"The End\"",
        "answerA": "\"The End\"",
        "answerB": "\"Peace Frog\"",
        "answerC": "\"The Celebration of the Lizard\" ",
        "answerD": "\"The Soft Parade\" "
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The anti- war classic \"Us and Them\" appears on what landmark progressive rock album by Pink Floyd? ",
        "correct": "Dark Side of the Moon",
        "answerA": "Dark Side of the Moon",
        "answerB": "Wish You Were Here",
        "answerC": "Meddle",
        "answerD": "The Wall"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-UK rock musician and singer Roger Waters named his 1992 record Amused to Death after this authors book of the same name.",
        "correct": "Neil Postman",
        "answerA": "Neil Postman",
        "answerB": "Marshall McLuhan",
        "answerC": "Harold Innis",
        "answerD": "Maxine Hancock"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Pink Floyd guitarist David Gilmore auctioned off 126 of his guitars in 2019 for what cause?",
        "correct": "Fighting climate change",
        "answerA": "Fighting climate change",
        "answerB": "Fighting militarism and war",
        "answerC": "Fighting racism and hate",
        "answerD": "Fighting violence against women"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This REM alternative youth anthem, released in 1986, regularly made top ten lists on FM radio stations for the greatest modern rock songs of all time.",
        "correct": "What's the song? \"It's the End of the World as We Know it (and I feel fine)\" ",
        "answerA": "What's the song? \"It's the End of the World as We Know it (and I feel fine)\" ",
        "answerB": "\"Radio Free Europe\"",
        "answerC": "\"Driver 8\"",
        "answerD": "\"What's the Frequency Kenneth?\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In 2017 Jennifer Saran teamed up with Ladysmith Black Mambazo, singer/ songwriter Narada Michael Walden, and this world famous guitarist to record \"Wake Up,\" a song about world inequality and poverty.",
        "correct": "Carlos Santana",
        "answerA": "Carlos Santana",
        "answerB": "Eddie Van Halan",
        "answerC": "Stevie Ray Vaughan",
        "answerD": "Chuck Berry"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Which Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young song was not on their 1970 album d�j� Vu?",
        "correct": "Southern Cross",
        "answerA": "Southern Cross",
        "answerB": "Woodstock",
        "answerC": "Teach Your Children",
        "answerD": "Our House"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What's the first song off the first album by the LA hip-hop group Cypress Hill?",
        "correct": "\"Pigs\"",
        "answerA": "\"Pigs\"",
        "answerB": "\"Street Fightin Ese\"",
        "answerC": "\"Insane in the Membrane\"",
        "answerD": "\"I Want to Get High\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-In what Door's song does the line \"We Want the World and We Want it Now!\" appear?",
        "correct": " \"When the Music's Over\"",
        "answerA": " \"When the Music's Over\"",
        "answerB": "\"LA Women\"",
        "answerC": "\"Not to Touch the Earth\"",
        "answerD": "\"The End\""
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Immortal Technique took the profits from his third album the 3rd World and helped to set up an orphanage in Kabul, Afghanistan after years of US intervention. What was this project called?",
        "correct": "The Green Light Project",
        "answerA": "The Green Light Project",
        "answerB": "The Red Light Project",
        "answerC": "The Blue Light Project",
        "answerD": "The Black Light Project"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-What's the name of MC5's first and (generally considered their best) album?",
        "correct": "Kick out the Jams",
        "answerA": "Kick out the Jams",
        "answerB": "High Times",
        "answerC": "Back in the U.S.A.",
        "answerD": "Motor City Five"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-Patti Smith recorded this landmark punk album in 1975. What was its name?",
        "correct": "Horses",
        "answerA": "Horses",
        "answerB": "Easter",
        "answerC": "Wave",
        "answerD": "Radio Ethiopia"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The song \"Ain't Gonna Let Nobody Turn Me Round\" was recorded by two artists in the 1960's. ",
        "correct": "Pete Seeger and the SNCC Freedom Singers",
        "answerA": "Pete Seeger and the SNCC Freedom Singers",
        "answerB": "Phil Ochs and the Justice Singers",
        "answerC": "Woody Guthrie and the Liberty Singers",
        "answerD": "Paul Robeson and Revolution Singers"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-This landmark 1988 alternative album by South Youth featured the song \"Teenage Riot.\" ",
        "correct": "Daydream Nation",
        "answerA": "Daydream Nation",
        "answerB": "Dirty",
        "answerC": "Goo",
        "answerD": "Evol"
    },
    {
        "question": "REBEL ROCKERS-The Irish musicians Bob Geldof and U2, have attacked this Burmese leader, accusing her of complicity in the ethnic cleansing of hundreds of thousands of Rohingya people.",
        "correct": "Aung San Suu Kyi",
        "answerA": "Aung San Suu Kyi",
        "answerB": "Corazon Aquino",
        "answerC": "Khin Kyi",
        "answerD": "Indira Gandhi"
    }
]